# KATELYN MICHALOVE

Senior Product Designer

katelynmichalove@gmail.com katelynmichalove.com

615-613-5617

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Sunbelt Rentals**

Senior Product Designer / May 2021 - Present

- Led a team of junior and mid level designers to completely redesign our eCommerce website.
- Created and presented design process for the team which shifted them to be data driven while pushing for what's best and compromising when necessary based on timeline and feasibility.

Product Designer / Aug 2020 - May 2021

- Created our new onboarding experience for our growing team including one to ones and visits to the field.
- Created personas and user journeys from past user research to lead and determine the feature set required for a B2B mobile application launch.
- Merged previous B2C mobile designs with the authenticated B2B website designs I had led in a previous project to create an omnichannel experience.

Junior Product Designer /July 2019 - Aug 2020

- Independently led the redesign of the authenticated space of sunbeltrentals.com and took designs from wireframe to launch.
- As a result of this initiative, time to task for paying invoices decreased by 50% while the amount of invoices paid online increased by 50%.

# **Procter and Gamble / Process Engineer**

Jun 2017 - Jul 2018

• Led troubleshooting for the chemical plant to solve for process improvement areas.

# **EDUCATION**

**University of Tennessee** / 2017 / BA Chemical Engineering

Bloc / 2019 / UX Design Apprenticeship

# **SUMMARY**

I am a Senior Product Designer with skills in conducting user research and leading projects from wireframe to launch. I am data-driven and seek out analytics, user research, and competitive insight to drive design decision. I collaborate with the team to define requirements and develop a product that solves users' problems while meeting business objectives.

### **TOOLS**

Sketch, Figma

Marvel, Invision

Adobe Creative Suite

Dovetail

Lookback

Miro, Figjam

Survey Gizmo/Alchemer

Git, GitHub

Google Analytics

HTML, CSS

Jira, Confluence

# **SKILL SET**

User Experience Design

User Research

Market Research

**Usability Testing** 

Information Architecture

Visual Design

**Branding** 

**Prototyping** 

Frontend Development